They're back... and deadlier than ever!
The Dirty Dozen: Next Mission is a action, war, tv
movie film directed by Andrew V. McLaglen.
Major Reisman is "volunteered" to lead another mission using convicted army
soldiers, sentenced to either death or long prison terms.
This time their mission is to kill a Nazi general
who plans to assassinate Hitler.
Maj. John Reisman, played by Lee Marvin.
Gen. Worden, played by Ernest Borgnine.
Louis Valentine, played by Ken Wahl.
Tommy Wells, played by Larry Wilcox.
Sam Sixkiller, played by Sonny Landham.
Sgt. Bowren, played by Richard Jaeckel.
The Dirty Dozen: Next Mission is a 1985 made-for-TV film and sequel to
the original 1967 film Dirty Dozen, directed by Andrew V.
McLaglen and reuniting Lee Marvin, Ernest Borgnine and Richard
Jaeckel 18 years after the original hit war film.
Marvin returns to lead an all-new dirty dozen on a mission to
assassinate SS General Sepp Dietrich, played by Wolf Kahler.
The film explores themes of army, prisoner, nazi, world war ii, sequel.